https://opticus.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Contact
Search for:
* Required
Forgot Your Password?
New Customer ?Sign up
All CategoriesTOOLS & ACCESSORIESSTRIPPERS & CLEANERSPRODUCT HIREOTDR TESTERSOPTICAL TESTERSOptical Power MetersHire SplicerHire OTDRFusion SplicerFIBRE OPTIC TRAININGDIGITAL TESTERSCONSULTANCYCOMPONENTSCLEAVERSAPPLICATION NOTES
Search for:
My cart
£0.00
0
shopping bag
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Categories
TOOLS & ACCESSORIESSTRIPPERS & CLEANERSPRODUCT HIREHire SplicerHire OTDROTDR TESTERSOPTICAL TESTERSOptical Power MetersFusion SplicerFIBRE OPTIC TRAININGDIGITAL TESTERSCONSULTANCYCOMPONENTSCLEAVERSAPPLICATION NOTES
Home
Hire
Catalogue
OTDRs
FUSION SPLICER
FIBRE OPTIC TRAINING
DIGITAL TESTERS
OPTICAL TESTERS
shopping bag
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Privacy Policy
Home » Privacy Policy
OPTICUS PRIVACY POLICY JANUARY 2019
PRIVACY POLICY: Opticus based at 1-1 Titan Enterprise, 1 Aurora Avenue, Clydebank G81 1BF are committed to preserving your privacy. You are receiving this communication because we are in the process of doing business with you or you have submitted a request for information from us. Any data such as your name, email address and telephone number will be stored securely and not passed to third parties without specifically asking you for permission. If you have requested information, we will answer your enquiry and this may include details of products, services, prices, offers, technical recommendations and tips. Under GDPR rules this is classed a Legitimate Interest to supply information to a potential or existing customer.
UNSUBSCRIBING: You can request us to stop communicating with you at any time by emailing us.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR DATA: The Data you provide to us is confidential and will not be disclosed to third parties unless you request this or in the event there is a legal requirement to do so.
SECURITY: We employ security measures to protect your Data from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction or damage. Please help us keep our records updated by informing us of any changes to your e-mail address and other contact details.
THIRD PARTY WEBSITES: Because we want your experience of the Opticus website to be as informative and useful as possible, we provide a number of links to websites operated by third parties (“Third Party Websites”). Please be aware that we do not control such Third Party Websites and that such Third Party Websites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. We assume no responsibility for the information gathering practices of Third Party Websites that you are able to access through our Site, and we encourage you to review each Third Party Website’s privacy policy before disclosing any personally identifiable information.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY: We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our Site.
YOUR RIGHTS: You have the right to ask for a copy of the Data held by us in our records. You also have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your Data.
COOKIES: If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. For users that register on our website, we store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time.
Newsletter
Subscribe to Newsletter
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Information
About us
Warranty
Contact us
How to order
Privacy Policy
Track your order
Partners
New products
Training Schedule
Make a Request
Request a Quote
Request a Callback
Product Category
TOOLS & ACCESSORIESAPPLICATION NOTESCLEAVERSCOMPONENTSCONSULTANCYDIGITAL TESTERSFIBRE OPTIC TRAININGFusion SplicerHire OTDRHire SplicerOptical Power MetersOPTICAL TESTERSOTDR TESTERSPRODUCT HIRESTRIPPERS & CLEANERS
Site MapHome
Catalogue
FIBRE OPTIC TRAINING
OTDR TESTERS
OPTICAL TESTERS
DIGITAL TESTERS
FUSION SPLICER
PRODUCT HIRE
Contact
Copyright Copyright ©2020 Opticus. All rights reserved.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Subject
Your Message
Top
Call Now ButtonThis website uses cookies to improve your browsing experience. Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
